Actually... We're vampires!
What?!
What the hell are you doing?!
MayoPan was a way for us
to interact with all of you humans.
Livestream to hit 1,000,000 subscribers!!
Make sure you subscribe!!
Good morning from the dead of night~   Streaming live from an abandoned hospital at night   Please subscribe, leave comments, and hit the like button!!
But unless we hit a million subs tonight,
our channel is going to be erased!
Live-sama, you're watching, aren't you?!
We're in big trouble!
So please, come back right away!
Live...
Where are you, and what are you doing?
And so, today's stream is...
Huh?
Oh! Now we have vampires
who are going to be "it"!
Vampires playing tag in an abandoned hospital!
Livestream to hit 1,000,000 subscribers!!
Make sure you subscribe!!
Good morning from the dead of night~   Streaming live from an abandoned hospital at night   Please subscribe, leave comments, and hit the like button!!
No stopping until we hit a million subs!
Vampire Tag in an Abandoned Hospital!!
No stopping?
If they catch you, then it's all over!
Hey, now, we didn't start yet.
Looks like they're serious!
Okay, then, to kick this off...
Let's begin this game of tag!
Man, this has gotten out of hand!
This way, morons!
The Game of Tag Begins!!
How do I put this all together?
Masaki-san.
Think the stream will be okay?
Somehow.
Thank you.
Also, Masaki-san...
Wait.
This stream is way too reckless!
Why did you reveal yourselves
in the first place?!
Now Mother will be on your—
Nobody watching believes any of it.
What?
stones: damn loud explosion
eelchair: What was that?!
wawawa: ?!?!
Extra Serving of Abura Soba: Which side
is it in vampire tag?
Please Listen to Me: Did something explode?
Such elaborate effects~
Obemura: Really funny joke there lolol
ribon: Where's Live-sama...?
17765: Wait... There's way too much
going on here
But we managed to lure out our hunters.
Now we can shoot a game of tag
like no one's seen before.
What if they catch you?
It'll be fine!
We won't let them get us!
2,581 watching now
It's true that the audience
is eating this up, but...
Obemura: Oh, look at them all run
ponsuke: this camera switching is really...
Chocolate Chip: What a serious game of tag
G7I5N: Are the staff amateurs?
Should have gotten pros...
Dim-Witted Kana: It just started and it's already
hard to see~ I don't know if I can watch this to the end
Sayacha: No way they'll hit a million subs
Flying Chicken: Please set up the cameras
so we can see everyone~~~
Running & Sneaker: We want to see more Fu
okapon: this camera work...
She really is such a pain in the butt.
Oh, there you are.
Jump!
Cling...
A wild gamble ain't so bad sometimes!
I'll make sure MayoPan lives on!
You won't get your hands on—
Livestream to hit 1,000,000 subscribers!!
Tokage's Out!!
Tokage!
Green Turtle: What's going on
Ke-boy: Her fault for smoking in a hospital
gomadanGO: No idea what's happening
since the camera work sucks so much.
ribon: Where's Live-sama...?
Wasshoi: These cameras kys kys kys
Gen: So hard to see ;w;
paka: How dare they do this to my Tokage-sama...!
Jshi66: they suck
Fried Mackerel Meal: Wait, isn't Fu in danger, too??
Fork Devil: Fu...
Engawa: Ah, not good
wawawa: Show us how the others are doing!
What?
Livestream to hit 1,000,000 subscribers!!
Masaki-san.
Huh?
Keep the stream going.
Don't let this be the end for MayoPan.
Everyone watching, thanks for tuning in.
Please! Keep spreading the word
about this stream!
Fu!
Livestream to hit 1,000,000 subscribers!!
Fu's Out!!
You said they wouldn't get you...
Who cares about that now?!
flapjack octopus: oh no
1000 km/h: They got Fu-chan too
Fork Devil: Fuuuuuuuuuuuu ;w;
www.jp: wait, did she just say masaki???
who-love-love: Don't you go scaring Fu
vckx: By Masaki, does she mean Masakichi?!
Jshi66: Masakichi?!
ribon: Where's Live-sama...?
Where's Live-sama...? Where's Live-sama...?
Mii: Is Fu okay? I'm so worried
Goemon: So Masakichi came up with this??
Yukko: Did you get proper permission
to film here?
Level-1200: Is Masakichi there?
Shut up already!
Wait, Ichiko! In front of you!
Masaki?!
Hold this!
This game of tag isn't over yet!
Right!
Ichiko!
Use the laptop to see where they are!
Um...
Goemon: Did I just hear Masakichi??
That's right!
Here with me is Masakichi!
Don't show my face! Where are they?
Um, they're...
We're done for.
Th-The jigsaw is up.
Damn it!
Yuki?!
Leave them to me.
Hurry up and run away!
Don't be absurd!
Yuki-sama, there's no way—
Just go on!
Or we'll all end up out!
Shigeyuki...
And don't call me Shigeyuki!
I'll take care of all of you.
Get ready!
Ichiko!
M-Masaki...
I'm bleeding!
What?!
First aid... We need first aid!
What was that?
Yuki?
Please Stand By
They got Yuki-sama...
Ichiko!
What do we do?
It's fine.
A quick nap'll heal me right up.
Masaki.
What is it?
The stream is going to end...
MayoPan is going to end!
I don't want that!
ribon: Where's Live-sama...?
Where's Live-sama...? Where's Live-sama...?
taiyaki: still not back?
Level-1200: Stop slacking
mumu: if only live was here...
G7I5N: Taking so long, I can't watch this
Takowasa: Stop trying to buy time for views
Flying Chicken: What's taking so long?
Vending Machine: Did they get permission
from the owner of this abandoned hospital?
If they didn't...
After we all tried so hard...
After you came to Banpai Manor...
Everything's been so much fun.
That's... That's why...
All I wanted was for that to last.
Masaki...
MayoPan's...
Ichiko? Ichiko!
I'm the only one left now.
coffee beans: not even funny
Iron Deficiency: Your ideas blow, just quit now
yani-yani: Stop streaming
aieuo: Masakichi trying to rack up viewers
Gen: Get on with it already. Don't keep us waiting
Passion Exploitation: What happened to all that
vampire stuff???
taiyaki: boring
Jelly-beans: Everyone! I saw a post saying
the stream is over!!
Praying Owl: Snoozefest, what a waste of time
masa: this is all masakichi's fault
rice on rice: she'll pay
ribon: Where's Live-sama...?
Where's Live-sama...? Where's Live-sama...?
Stalemate Gamer: Awful stream.
Give me my time back
eeeeeeks: What a creep.
This is...
where I first met Live!
Ah, damn it all!
This is all Live's fault!
Where the hell is she?!
Images
Title
Please stand by
For end of stream
I swear...
Lonely Oedo Girl
"Oedo"...
"Ah, another one of Masakichi's ideas?"
Work: So many trolls lol
energy: Please do something about this
Lemon Sour: Is it coming back?
Lonely Oedo Girl: Ah, another one
of Masakichi's ideas? Whenever she
gets stoked, it always ends in trouble
Lonely Oedo Girl: Hilarious how she
hasn't changed at all since the
Hype-Sis days
Whenever she gets stoked,
it always ends in trouble!
Hilarious how she hasn't changed
at all since the Hype-Sis days!
Huh?
Lonely Oedo Girl: So now she's ruining MayoPan?
So now she's ruining MayoPan?
Lonely Oedo Girl: Oh, is she suddenly going to turn things around
for some real hype?
Oh, is she suddenly going to turn
things around for some real hype?
"I can't wait!"
Lonely Oedo Girl: I can't wait lmao
Huh?!
What the hell's your deal?!
I mean...
You're Masakichi-san, right?
I'm a huge fan!
That's what you said!
So why this?!
What's even going through your head?!
Do you know what I've gone through
because of comments like yours?!
Get a life, you goddamn idiot!
Is she just having fun stirring the pot?
Am I taking this way too seriously?
Lonely Oedo Girl: Ah, another one of Masakichi's ideas? Whenever she gets stoked, it always ends in trouble
Lonely Oedo Girl: Hilarious how she hasn't changed
at all since the Hype-Sis days
Lonely Oedo Girl: So now she's ruining MayoPan? lmao
Lonely Oedo Girl: Oh, is she suddenly going to
turn things around for some real hype?
Lonely Oedo Girl: I can't wait lmao
mumu: If Live was here...
If the abuser wants to show her face, then go ahead
I wouldn't mind seeing Masakichi. In a lot...
Go away scumbag
thxbye: I wouldn't mind seeing Masakichi. In...
Asahitaro: Go away scumbag
Momo: To tell you the truth, I don't hate Masakichi
that much either...
dedesuke: [Newsflash] Masakichi on the run
[Newsflash] Masakichi on the run [Newsflash] Masakichi
on the run [Newsflash] Masakichi on the run [Newsflash]
Masakichi on the run [Newsflash] Masakichi on the run
chelly-blossoms: I'll always be Masakichi-san's fan
Sakura?
Of course there are people out there
who really hate me,
as well as those having fun trolling.
But there are also people who support me.
A very small number, but still.
No matter how much I try, I don't understand!
I can't tell how any of these
people feel about me!
I never will, and when all's
said and done, I'm scared!
But one thing's for sure!
watching now
Everyone's here to watch MayoPan.
Our haters...
and our supporters!
So no matter what anyone thinks...
I've gotta continue the stream!
Livestream to hit 1,000,000 subscribers!!
Good morning from the dead of night!
Mayonaka Punch!
Staff member Masakichi here!
Yep.
Livestream to hit 1,000,000 subscribers!!
"How dare you show your face on camera?"
You're absolutely right.
However...
However!
I can't let this livestream end!
I can't let this be the end for MayoPan!
So I have a favor to ask you all!
Let me join in on this game of tag.
And so, I'm the only one left now!
If they catch me,
the stream will immediately end!
But I won't lose!
You may be surprised to hear
that I'm pretty dang good at tag!
Yes, that's right.
I'm a nasty piece of work—
What?
I'm the one who made a
huge mess of Hype-Sis.
And I'm to blame for this as well!
For saying such awful things to Live!
So that's why...
That's why Live, all of MayoPan,
the Hype-Sis girls...
and all of you watching
deserve an apology from me.
I'm really sorry!
I know it's not something an apology will fix.
Still, I don't want to say goodbye to MayoPan!
If there's anyone out there who wants
to show their support for MayoPan,
spread the word about this stream!
I, Masakichi, won't let myself
be caught until Live shows up!
Vampires Playing Tag in an Abandoned Hospital! No Stopping Until We Hit a Million Subs!!
MayoPan's going all out as usual, I see.
It's not much, but the least
I can do is lend a hand.
Send
MayoPan helped me out at TSUMA FES Extreme, and they've got an
interesting stream going right now! Please give it a look! Bomber!!
Mayonaka Punch   @mayopan
Good morning from the dead of night!
Today's gonna be a day to remember!! Get ready to stay up all night~ <3
Bomber!
TSUMA-shi   @tsumashi
MayoPan helped me out at TSUMA FES Extreme, and they've got an
interesting stream going right now! Please give it a look! Bomber!!
Mayonaka Punch   @mayopan
Good morning from the dead of night!
Today's gonna be a day to remember!! Get ready to stay up all night~ <3
Vampires Playing Tag in an Abandoned Hospital!
No Stopping Until We Hit a Million Subs!!
NewTube
watching now
There's no way you're getting your hands on me!
Catch me if you can!
Sorry, Live.
Ever since we met, you've
always been thinking about me.
That's why...
I'll keep up this game of tag,
even if I break my leg!
Feudal Lord: Masakichi's doing better than...
hipopo: Seriously, go away
Cheese Naan: We don't need Masakichi, just find...
...cone: violent bitch kys kys
Lonely Oedo Girl: Lol wow
she's really running. Good luck~
Remy: So intense lmao
Claire: TSUMA-shi sent me here!
Must be exhausting~ Good luck!!
daniel: You're nobody, don't get cocky
Vampires Playing Tag in an Abandoned Hospital! No Stopping Until We Hit a Million Subs!!
cherry-blossoms: Masakichi, you can do it!!
flapjack octopus: so much for the vampire stuff lmao
Terrarium: TSUMA-shi recommended this stream...
I'll be silently cheering you on!
watching now
hinoko: You're pretty athletic!! My opinion...
Fork Devil: If Masakichi survives...
Fu will be saved, so I'm on your side!
ny...nyold it~ ny...nyold it~ ny...nyold it~
Boiled Tofu: What's entertaining about this stream?
What's entertaining about this stream?
Give up already!
This game's not over yet!
You've all lost.
Stop the stream.
D-Don't move!
If you come any closer...
Why did you decide to do it?
What?
Why did you decide to be on camera?
Huh?
For MayoPan!
Not to mention everyone watching!
Listen up!
If we reach a million subs,
I want all of them back!
And Banpai Manor—
No.
I'm asking about you.
What are you talking about?
That doesn't matter—
Answer me.
Like I said, so MayoPan can live on.
That's all it is.
This may be an atrocious idea
that doesn't make any sense,
but they gave their all for it!
That's why...
Even though I know no one wants to watch me...
Ah, never mind!
Everyone, forget what I just said!
Anyway, I'll do everything I can
until Live comes back...
Huh?
No way.
Vampires Playing Tag in an Abandoned Hospital! No Stopping Until We Hit a Million Subs!!
10k watching now
When did all these people...
In the end, I...
Let me ask you one more time.
Why did you decide to be on camera?
I...
Visiting an abandoned hospital!!
I mean, that's obvious, isn't it?!
Because... Because... Because...
Because I want to, of course!
The truth is, I want to feel wanted.
Even now, I want them to enjoy watching me.
But I know that's too much to ask.
Live!
You're watching this stream, aren't you?!
I showed my face!
I didn't run away this time!
Did you forget our deal?!
You promised me, didn't you?!
To make a meal of me
once we hit a million subs!
So hurry up and show yourself already!
I won't let myself be caught just yet!
I'm not gonna make it.
No, no, no!
I'll make sure the stream goes on!
I won't let it all end here!
Gotcha.
I'm here for you, Masaki.
What took you so long?!
Sorry.
No, I was in the wrong.
Live, I'm sorry for all
the awful things I said.
It's fine.
I'm just glad I could hear it.
Hear what?
How you really felt.
That you wanted to be in our videos.
You knew already, didn't you?
You're the vampire who knows me
better than anyone else, after all.
I wanted to hear you say it!
So I'm really happy!
Yeah.
Huh?
You're happy you heard me say it?
Yep!
Live, you heard us talking just now?
Hey, wait a minute!
Wait, that means...
Huh? What?
Huh?!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
It went off without a hitch.
What a relief.
Masakichi's back in action.
The hunters were...
Us Outside Kids, and...
Hype-Sis!
Tokage-nee-san, your athletic skills
are, like, totally out there!
Whoo...
I mean, that's obvious, isn't it?
Because, because, because...
Because I want to, of course!
Okay, everyone! All together now!
You got pranked!
You Got Pranked!
You Got
Pranked!!
Impeccable timing, Mastamin-nee-san.
Don't call me Mastamin-nee-san.
"Would Masakichi Show Up on Stream for MayoPan?"
You Got Pranked!
Well, then...
So sorry for making all of you worry!
Man, I know, right?
I didn't think it'd all work out this well!
All righty, time to explain how it went down!
Oh, hold that thought!
Masakichi, why don't we—
You bastard...
Screw you!
Live-sama!
We sincerely apologize for putting on
this preposterous stream.
It all started when Masakichi ran out of
the house, refusing to star in our videos,
which was when I came up with this prank.
We'll explain all the nitty-gritty
details later in a separate video.
Huh? Vampires?
Of course there's no such thing!
Anyway!
We're really...
Very sorry about what we did!
You got all of them involved.
Wait, if it was you under this mask,
were you the one who attacked our car?
Th-That was me.
I immediately changed my outfit
to meet up with you.
What about Banpai Manor?
Just normal repairs!
For a house that might get torn down?
What about Ai-san, then?
I came up with that one!
Changing one letter in Live gives you Love!
That's what "Ai" means!
Ai
So the part about Live remembering
what happened twenty years ago...
Oh, that part's true!
What?
Man, the two of us really are
fated to be together!
Huh?!
Don't worry about it.
Well, then... Once again,
let's aim for one million!
We have one month left!
Oh, right.
Today being the deadline was a lie as well.
Once we reach it, I can go ahead, right?
What?
I can make a meal of you, right?
That's null and void now.
What?!
We're truly, truly sorry
about our past livestream!
Not you too, Shigeyuki.
Oh, but it's all okay!
Not a single person who watched
believes that vampires exist!
Right?
Right? Right?
It seems this served as a good
opportunity for that human, Masaki.
Y-Yes!
I have to say, the bonds between
Live and Masaki are strong indeed!
They certainly are.
Agh! I'm sick and tired of being a vampire!
What's wrong with going out during the day?!
I-I'm done for...
Huh?
A talking bat.
Are you okay?
L-Let me have some blood!
Go ahead. Make a meal of me.
Here.
Time to dig in!
Chomp!!
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Go away, you dumb bat!
It hurts!
Are you okay, Masaki-chan?
She saved Live's life, after all.
So that's why she can't forget that taste?
Well, she ended up sleeping
for twenty years after that.
We're home!
Tokage-san, you can park the car over there.
Sheesh, why's it my job...
Masaki...
I'm sorry! I mean it, really!
But you know, that prank was
my way of showing how much I care!
Well, I don't know...
I'll work even harder on
our videos starting tomorrow!
I'll make sure we hit a million subs!
So our deal about your blood...
Ah, sure, fine.
I'll consider it.
No backsies, okay?!
Let's go shoot a video together right now!
Hey!
What are you two ditching for?!
Hey, Live!
Can you slow it down a bit?!
Masaki, thanks.
Huh? For what?
For teaching us all about videos.
And bringing us out into the world
from the darkness.
You did the same for me.
All right!
Here we go!
Good morning from the dead of night!